Is everything ready?
To answer the Immortal,
everything is ready in the main hall.
Lead the way.
Let's go.
Please.
Tonight at the Hour of Xu,
divide into seven groups,
eight people each.
Announcing Huaming Road.
It must be done before the Hour of Hai.
Yes.
Dry weather and dry things.
Be careful with fire.
It's the third watch.
Sister.
Do you need me for something?
I have a question.
I don't know if I should ask.
Ask away.
Are you a monster?
What?
Afraid I'll eat you?
No, no, no.
I've just never seen
such a beautiful and kind monster like you.
Little brat.
Sister.
Then what kind of monster are you?
Can you teach me your magic?
Sister, please teach me.
Master, they are all buried.
Rise.
I have set up a barrier in Ercheng.
If any monsters enter the city,
I will definitely know.
Master.
We've made such a big fuss.
What if the monster doesn't come?
Don't worry.
The ancestor is here.
They'll definitely come.
Don't leave things to chance.
This battle is inevitable.
This Golden Immortal really looks down on us.
Let's go.
Let's teach the High Immortal a good lesson.
You're pretending to sleep.
Master, Master!
Come in.
You...
What's wrong?
The people...
They have all disappeared.
What?
Why are you here?
I...
Never mind that.
The people have disappeared.
Right.
All the people are gone!
Who found out first?
I did.
It was around the hour of Chen.
I went out for breakfast,
only to find none of the shops were open.
I searched every house,
and then I realized
that everyone in the city had disappeared.
What should we do, Immortal?
Ercheng has at least tens of thousands of people.
How could they all disappear overnight
without a trace?
It must be a monster.
Such a massive movement of people,
yet not a sound.
Ancestor,
the inescapable net you laid out
didn't detect anything either?
It seems the intruder...
Not an ordinary person.
Hahaha, hahaha.
Hahahaha.
The rabbit jumps, the dog barks.
Silk threads pull, making me smile.
The heart beats.
Chewing in the mouth.
Human hearts are like paper for me to manipulate.
Why is there no response?
Stepping on the positions of the Big Dipper.
The Hu family ancestor accompanies me.
In such a hurry.
The people of Sitiantai are so rude.
You didn't even say a word
before taking our people away.
Are you fit to speak of manners?
Where are the people of Ercheng?
I ate them.
Ate them?
Ate them? Ate them? Ate them?
What? Ate them?
Ate them.
Ate them?
Hahaha.
You are so stupid.
There are tens of thousands of people in Ercheng.
How could I eat them all?
Hahaha.
My lord.
You came here
to find me.
It has nothing to do with the locals.
Don't involve the innocent.
So you are the Golden Immortal.
Your aura seems quite ordinary.
Monster, watch your mouth!
My master's aura
is not something a wild demon like you can judge!
A wild demon?
You're courting death!
Now that's some aura.
It seems
you don't intend to let the people go easily.
What do you think?
Bullying the few with the many?
I'd like to see,
before you kill me,
how many people I can kill.
Do you not care about the lives of the people?
Wild monster,
don't underestimate us.
Found it.
Save them.
There are too many.
I need some time.
Slay the demons first.
Jinwang.
Pingjie Qianghaihui.